http://www.grncorp.com/about/privacy.aspx

Privacy Policy
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for Global Recruiters
Network. This privacy notice applies solely to
information collected by this web site.
Your data will be stored and processed in whole or in part in the United
States. The information we gather on the our site may be shared within the
Global Recruiters Network-affiliated companies on a worldwide basis in order
to deliver the products and services we offer to employers such as searches
for job seekers or in order to undertake analysis of our database such as
aggregate profiling of our registered users.
The Global Recruiters Network site may contain
links to other Web sites over which we have no control. We are not
responsible for the privacy policies or practices of other Web sites to
which you choose to link from our Sites. We encourage you to review the
privacy policies of those other Web sites so you can understand how they
collect, use and share your information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only
have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or
other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to
anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you
contacted us.
We will not share your information with any third party outside of our
organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to a
potential employer.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to
tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this
privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do
the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone
number given on our website: See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit
sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both
online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data),
that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can
verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web
browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web
page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted
online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need
the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer
service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The
computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are
kept in a secure environment.
Your Acceptance of our Privacy Practices
By using this website or any other GRN website or interactive banner ads, you signify your acceptance of our Privacy Policy and your adherence to the terms and conditions posted on the website. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes here in order to keep you informed.
If you have any questions or concerns about the security at our website, please feel free to Contact Us.
Terms of Use
This site is owned and operated by Global Recruiters Network, Inc. ("GRN"). GRN and GRN franchised offices provide services to you subject to the following notices, terms, and conditions. In addition, when you use any service from this site, you will be subject to the rules, guidelines, policies, terms, and conditions applicable to such service. By using this site, you agree to these Terms of Use. GRN may revise these terms and conditions at any time, in its sole discretion, by updating this posting. Please visit this page periodically to review the terms and conditions, since they are binding upon you.
Copyright
All content included on this site, such as text, graphics, logos, button icons, images, audio clips, and software, is the property of GRN or its content suppliers and is protected by U.S. and international copyright laws. The compilation (meaning the collection, arrangement, and assembly) of all content on this site is the exclusive property of GRN and is protected by U.S. and international copyright laws. All technology used on this site is the property of GRN or its suppliers and is protected by U.S. and international copyright laws. Any use, including the reproduction, modification, distribution, transmission, republication, display, or performance, of the content on this site is strictly prohibited.
Trademarks
"Global Recruiters", "GRN", and "grncorp.com" is a registered trademark of GRN in the United States and other countries. "GRN" graphics, logos, and service names are trademarks of GRN. GRN's trademarks may not be used in connection with any product or service that is not GRN's in any manner that is likely to cause confusion among customers, or in any manner that disparages or discredits GRN.
Use of Site
This site or any portion of this site may not be reproduced, duplicated, copied, sold, resold, or otherwise exploited for any commercial purpose that is not expressly permitted by GRN Corporate. GRN and its affiliates and GRN Offices reserve the right to refuse service, terminate accounts, and/or cancel orders in their discretion, including, without limitation, if they believe that customer conduct violates applicable law or is harmful to their interests.
LIMITS ON LIABILITY
GRN AND GRN OFFICES SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR:
THE CONTENTS OF ANY COMMUNICATION, MESSAGE OR INFORMATION PROVIDED TO THEM BY YOU OR OTHER THIRD PARTIES;
THE CONTENTS OF ANY WEB SITE NOT CONTROLLED, OWNED, OR OPERATED BY GRN THAT IS ACCESSED FROM OR LINKED TO THE THIS SITE BY DIRECT OR INDIRECT MEANS;
ANY DAMAGES OR INJURY CAUSED BY, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO, ANY FAILURE OF PERFORMANCE, ERROR, OMISSION, INTERRUPTION, DEFECT, DELAY IN OPERATION OF TRANSMISSION, COMPUTER VIRUS, OR LINE FAILURE; AND
ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, TORT, STRICT LIABILITY OR OTHERWISE, ARISING OUT OF OR RELATING TO USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE THIS WEB SITE, EVEN IF GRN HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. BECAUSE SOME STATES DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, THE ABOVE LIMITATION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. IF THIS LIMITATION OF LIABILITY OR THE EXCLUSION OF WARRANTY SET FORTH BELOW IS HELD INAPPLICABLE OR UNENFORCEABLE FOR ANY REASON, THEN GRN'S MAXIMUM LIABILITY TO YOU FOR ANY TYPE OF DAMAGE FOR ALL CLAIMS ARISING FROM THE USE OF THIS SITE SHALL BE LIMITED TO U.S. $100.00.
If you are dissatisfied with any portion of this site, or with any of these Terms of Use, your sole and exclusive remedy is to discontinue using the Web site.
Disclaimer
THIS SITE IS PROVIDED BY GRN ON AN "AS IS" BASIS. GRN MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, AS TO THE OPERATION OF THE SITE OR THE INFORMATION, CONTENT, MATERIALS, SERVICES OR PRODUCTS INCLUDED ON THIS SITE. TO THE FULL EXTENT PERMISSIBLE BY APPLICABLE LAW, GRN DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. GRN WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES OF ANY KIND ARISING FROM THE USE OF THIS SITE, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, PUNITIVE, AND CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES.
Indemnification
You agree to defend and indemnify and hold harmless GRN and GRN Offices and their officers, directors, employees, agents, successors, assigns and affiliates from and against any claims, actions and demands arising out of or relating to your use of this Web Site or any alleged breach of these Terms of Use.
Jurisdiction
This site is owned and operated by GRN from the state of Illinois, United States of America. GRN makes no representations that materials in this Site are appropriate or available for use in other locations, or that the Site may be lawfully viewed or downloaded outside of the United States. These Terms of Use and any claims relating in any fashion to this Site or its materials shall be governed by the laws of the State of Illinois applicable to contracts entered into and performed exclusively in Illinois, and you and GRN hereby consent to the exclusive jurisdiction and venue for any action or dispute arising out of or relating to such claims or these Terms of Use or your use of the Web Site, in the state or federal courts located in Wheaton, DuPage County, Illinois, United States of America. If any provisions of these Terms of Use and those of any other agreement you enter into with GRN regarding your use of the Site is found to be invalid by any court having competent jurisdiction, the invalidity of such provision shall not affect the validity of the remaining terms and conditions, which shall remain in full force and effect. No waiver of any term or condition shall be deemed a further or continuing waiver of such term or any other term. No changes to these terms and conditions may be made except by revised posting on this page by GRN.
ALL RIGHTS RESERVED
Except as expressly provided herein, nothing on this Site confers or is to be construed as conferring any license or right under any patent, copyright, trademark or other right of GRN or any third party. Any and all rights not expressly granted herein are reserved by GRN.
Contact Us
Global Recruiters Network, Inc
200 S. Wacker Drive, Suite 1300Chicago, IL 60606 USA
Say Hello
Phone: 630.663.1900
Toll Free: 866.476.8200
Fax: 630.663.1919
Keep Connected
Copyright © 2020 Global Recruiters Network, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
Our Privacy Policy..GRN and Global Recruiters Network, Brad Baiocchi CEO.
